Charles B. Gunn Collection 1988.0001
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series III: Photographs, undated, 1927-1985
  - Subseries C: Other subjects
    - People -- Charles E. Williams, General Passenger Traffic Manager, Boston, (1988-0001.ph1431-ph1434), undated (Box 21, Folder 247)
    - People -- Employees in Purchasing and Material Department (1988-0001.ph1435-ph1438), undated (Box 21, Folder 248)
    - People -- Employees -- Groups (1988-0001.ph1439-ph1454), ca. 1955 (Box 21, Folder 249)
    - Stadiums -- Hartford, Connecticut (North Meadows) (1988-0001.ph1697-ph1709), June 1955 (Box 24, Folder 270)
    - Tracks -- New Canaan, Connecticut (1988-0001.ph2100-ph2101), September 1954 (Box 25, Folder 315)
    - War damage (in Germany and other unidentified locations in Europe), taken by Charles Gunn while serving in the army during World War II (1988-0001.ph1455-ph1467), 1945 (Box 21, Folder 250)
    - Madiera-Mamore Railroad in Brazil (1988-0001.ph1468-ph1489), 1957 (Box 21, Folder 251)
    - Unidentified photographs (1988-0001.ph1490-ph1493), undated (Box 21, Folder 252)
    - Unidentified photographs (1988-0001.ph2102-ph2124), January 1955, June 1955, undated (Box 25, Folder 316)
    - Large mounted photographs of workfloor of the Cheshire Plastics Company and an unidentified city road construction scene (1988-0001.ph1605-ph1606), undated (Box 22, Folder 258)
- Series IV: Scrapbooks, 1955
  - Large aerial photographs of the damage to locations in Connecticut from the Floods of August, 1955, taken by Samuel Kravitt (1988-0001.ph1494-ph1531), 1955 August (Box 23, Folder 253)
  - Large aerial photographs of the damage to locations in Connecticut, Massachusetts, and Rhode Island from the Floods of August, 1955, taken by Samuel Kravitt (1988-0001.ph1532-ph1572), 1955 August (Box 23, Folder 254)